What's all this?
You see,
weren't we short on latrines before?
I plan to turn my room into a latrine.
Come in and take a look.
The Master just passed away,
yet here you are, busy digging a latrine.
What a good Young Master.
I never expected
that underneath the Sheng Family's house,
such a massive secret room was hidden.
Young Master, this place is like a maze.
It's all dead ends.
The Dragon-Seeking Ruler must be broken.
The ruler isn't broken.
The paths are changing.
These walls
seem to be moving slowly.
We've been going in circles.
A Living Maze.
Someone's here.
Guiding Wraith.
This crying sound...
is the wind blowing through the cracks,
distorted by the strange structure.
Not this way.
What are you crying for?
The real path is where crying is faintest.
Over there.
Lingyu.
Now we're just a widow and her orphan.
The Sheng Family relies entirely on you.
Madam, Master Qi and his son are here.
Oh, Brother Sheng.
How could you just leave us?
Cousin.
Sister-in-law, I brought a small gift
to comfort Brother Qiufeng's soul.
Thank you. Thank you.
And what about this?
This is a betrothal gift.
Since my brother has passed away,
I can't just watch a widow and her orphan
suffer like this.
The Qi and Sheng Families will now be one.
You...
Uncle, my father's body is not yet cold!
Lingyu.
Don't worry.
I'll treat you very well from now on.
I'll help you manage the Sheng Family.
I don't agree.
Do you even have a say here?
What right do you have to disagree?
You've only been married in for a few days.
Lingyu was in danger in the secret room,
and Master Sheng died suddenly.
Zhang Tianyou, are you trying to ruin us?
Master!
Father!
Master! Master!
Do you still have some unfulfilled wishes?
Brother Sheng's vital energy hasn't faded.
He has something to say.
Quick, take out that...
Get the Qi Family Soul-Continuation Talisman!
Here, Father.
Oh, Brother Sheng.
Tomorrow our families will be united.
As your brother, I
don't have much ability.
But the estate you left behind,
I will manage it well for you.
Especially your wife and your daughter.
I will take very good care of them for you.
Don't stare at me with such wide eyes.
Say something!
Master Qi.
You haven't mastered the Qi talisman book.
The Soul-Continuation Talisman
is drawn like this.
Don't move!
Alright.
Rest assured.
This Earth Vein Incantation Scripture...
I've already retrieved it for you.
Earth Vein Incantation Scripture!
I...
Master, I'll look after the Sheng Family.
I will save the Sheng residence. Rest in peace.
Master!
Father!
Brother Sheng!
No, Brother Sheng!
How could you hand the Sheng Family to him?
Get up and say something!
What are you doing?
Madam Sheng,
this kid clearly used dark magic!
This isn't normal!
The Master's dying wish is clear.
The Sheng Family does not welcome you.
See the guests out!
You...
Master Qi, Young Master Qi, please.
I... I will be back!
Zhang Tianyou, we're not done yet!
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Young Master,
what just happened to Master Sheng...
During rigor mortis,
limbs intermittently react to stimulation.
There's a dead body in here!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
What is this?
The Sheng Family scripture tossed like trash?
And you were sitting on it?
Tell us.
Why is a Sheng Family item in your hands?
Didn't you all just see it?
The old man handed the Sheng Family to me.
Just you?
That's right.
Just me.
Zhang Tianyou.
Sheng Lingyu.
If you want to be the Qi Family young madam,
you can go right now.
I won't stop you.
But I'm in charge of the Sheng Family now.
Zhang Tianyou,
you almost fooled me.
Zhang Tianyou!
Don't think stealing Master's things lets you rule!
Lingyu.
The Sheng Family cannot fall to the Qi Family.
And it certainly can't fall to this loser.
Go to the Qi Family now and find Qi Tiankun.
Get him under your control.
Understood.
Bastard.
I saw this coming.
It wouldn't be that easy.
Time to find a new wife.
Young Master,
You know the Sheng Family incantation scriptures,
and understand the Qi Family talisman books.
Who exactly are you?
Because the Sheng Family incantation scriptures
and the Qi Family's talisman books,
I read them when I was very young.
What did you say?
I said,
If we can't gather the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye,
and before the next full moon,
we can't find the Tidal Tomb,
The Four Great Families can't escape their fate.
Time is running out.
Who is it? Have you no manners?
Who's there?